European style.
(Leonard:)You can recognize people
on Google Earth?
(Howard:)Of course not. I got a buddy of mine
at NORAD to have a spy drone fly over.
(Leonard:)NORAD? You're using military aircraft?
(Howard:)It was already targeted
to poke around a nuclear reactor in Siberia.
(Howard:)I took it an hour out of its way, tops.
(Penny(entering, angry):)Okay, where is he?
Sheldon? I dropped him off
at the comic book store.
(Penny:)Here. Try and go online.
- Problem with the Wi-Fi?
- No, just try.
Greetings, hamburger-toucher.
(Sheldon(on screen):)You are probably wondering
why you cannot IM with your little friends...
(Sheldon(on screen):)...about how much you
heart various things.
(Sheldon(on screen):)Well, this recorded message
is alerting you...
(Sheldon(on screen):)...that I am putting an end to your
parasitic piggybacking upon our Wi-Fi.
(Sheldon(on screen):)If you want to remedy the situation...
(Sheldon(on screen):)...you can contact the phone company,
set up your own Wi-Fi and pay for it...
(Sheldon(on screen):)...or you may apologize to me.